Guide to the Records of the Alternative Media Center and and Interactive Telecommunications Program, Tisch School of the Arts RG.35.2
New York University Archives
- Series II: Alternative Media Center Publications and Papers, 1974-1986, undated
  - The Interactive Telecommunications Laboratory: A Proposal, 1978 August (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Progress Report Telecommunications Project, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Establishing A Telephone Conferencing System: The Dynamics of Doing It, 1980 September (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - The Telecommunications Market of the Eighties, 1981 October 19 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Educational and Other Two-way Cable Television Services in the United States, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - The Interactive Videodisc in the Study of Physics, 1983 July (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Video Games and Human Development, 1983 May 22-24 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Graphics Software for Teaching Communications Technology: Preliminary Proposal, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Two-Way Cable Television: An Evaluation of Community Uses in Reading, Pennsylvania, 1978 April (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Alternative Media Center Publications, 1974-1989 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Series IV: Photographic Materials, 1970-1979, undated
  - ITP Events (1 of 2), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - ITP Events (2 of 2), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - ITP Events -- Reading Consortium, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - BCTV -- HE, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Publi-Cable Conference, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cape May -- NCTA Conference, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Rejects, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Workbook, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Reading/SL, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Profiles, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - AMC People/Friends, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Negatives -- BCTV, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Coord. Workshop N.Y., circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Wash. Hts., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - AMC Publication Shots, circa 1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Monitor Shots, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Bakersfield, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - VAC, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Alternative Media Center Photos (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Alternative Media Center Photos (2 of 2), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Vermont, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Manhattan PS. 41, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - West VA., circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Reading Workshop, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (1 of 5), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (2 of 5), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (3 of 5), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (4 of 5), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (5 of 5), circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - ITP Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - ITP Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Series V: ADJACENT, December 2018-ongoing; 4 websites in 4 archived websites.
  Scope and Contents
  Topics covered in articles of the journal include bias in algorithms, "tech-enabled apophenia," machine learning libraries, feminism, simulations, colonialism, resistance, COVID-19, feelings, disembodiment, ritual, nature, media, technology, art, science, spirituality, and humanity. The websites contains information about the journal and links to each of its published issues.
  Accruals
  Accrued annually.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Appraisal
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored. Scope was expanded to include Google documents and YouTube and Vimeo videos.
  Historical Note
  ADJACENT is an online journal published by the Interactive Telecommunications Program at NYU. The first issue was published in September 2017. The journal focuses on emerging interactive media and research and analysis on contemporary issues.